Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology Admissions Office records, 1925-2002.
New York State College of Human Ecology Admissions Office records, 1925-2002.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Human Ecology Admissions Office records, 1925-2002.
23-11-2928
New York State College of Human Ecology. Admissions Office.
.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, memoranda, studies, profiles, statistics, publications, reports, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, memoranda, studies, profiles, statistics, publications, reports, and other records of the office.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, memoranda, studies, profiles, statistics, publications, reports, and other records of the office.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology. Admissions Office.; Cornell University--Administration.; New York State College of Home Economics.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also collection #23-2-2817, New York State College of Human Ecology records, Boxes 107-109 contain admissions brochures
CONTAINER LIST
- Early Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925, 1932, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Study on Admissions Responsibility and Criteria, pre-1967-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Admissions Profile, 1966, 1969, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Admissions Report, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Recommended Program of Study for Bachelor's Candidates Preparing for International Home Economics Assignments, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Reports on Undergraduates, 1974-1975, 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Admissions Reports and Highlights, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Admissions Annual Reports, 1960, 1981-1982, 1982-1983, 1983-1984, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Three Year Enrollment Plan, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Reports: "Ten Years in Admissions 1977-1988," "Ten Years in Student Services 1978-1988," Statistical Reports - 1973-1988, Twelve Year Comparison of Freshmen - 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minority Statistics, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Profiles of Classes, Late 1980s-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Student Services Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Student Services Annual Reports, 1981-1982, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "The Interchange"-a publication, March and April of 1986, September 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Admissions Report, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
- Degrees granted 1976-1977, Profile of Class of 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Admissions Facts, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Admissions Policy Committee Minutes - 1990s (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Admissions Policy Committee, September 1981-May 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Admissions Policy Committee, April 1980-August 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Admissions Policy Committee, 1976-March 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Publication - "Hotline", 1981-1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Publications, Brochures (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
- Application for Admissions and Program for Freshman Orientation, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Article from Time Magazine about the C.U. Admissions process - October 23, 2000 (Box 2)
- Registration Statistics, 1932-1962 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Sub-Committee on Secondary Education Curriculum - Annual Reports 1966-1969; Resident Educational Policies Committee - In Absentia Study - 1956, 1956-1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Admissions Statistics, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Sample Admissions Questionnaire (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Memos, Activities, Programs, 1989-1990s (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Powerpoint - "A Snapshot: Human Ecology Undergraduate Affairs", 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Admissions Facts, 2006, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Models for Working with Undergraduates in Research, January 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Summer Jobs of Undergraduates and Reports on Graduates of the Class of 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)